you've got north facing to north south
facing to south
and you try if you go on you rotate and
roll around one way
sideways never rolls over
it's a big fight to roll a a compass or
magnet and field over they spin sideways
easy as pipe
so you understand what happens here you
actually would be rotated this way
fighting against all the other fields
but the normal fields runs either and
they can assist
understand because you won't just tap
into north and south pole
you've got north south east west
and all degrees in between
that's funny how do you think your
electricity comes off there
yeah how does it come off does it come
off
horizontal or vertical does it come off
towards north pole does it come off
towards south pole
does it come off north and south pole
and if it does
is it going vertical to do that or is it
going horizontal
all these things you know take place
they yeah fisher and pikel for use for a
second i know
nothing about them as such okay
the fisher and pikel they have actually
got
a whole lot of coils on the center of
your washing machine drum
and then what they've got is embedded
into grey plastic
and so on you've got square magnets and
what actually happens is
they're flipping feels electrically and
everything else in the coils
so your washing machine will do that
they're going to sand
and they can also spin it up and right
now that's all in a big hub like that on
the bottom of your washer machine
now what they found is you don't need
all the big bunches of wires and
everything else but if you feed in a
very small amount
of power the opposite way around the
damn magnets and the
and the coils will output more power
than what you ever used to put into to
do anything it's already built
and all you need to do if you want to
get more out of them is actually don't
change your coils because the belt wide
run
everything else change the magnets step
your magnets out turn your magnets
around in for ends instead of side to
side
then you have something that they don't
even know about and tell you about
instead
and if you don't if you don't use a flat
side of a magnet
why not um curve a magnet on the end
sort of like the old um
magnetos they had the horseshoe magnets
and they played up in the horseshoe
they played in that hook they never
played where the fields are on the end
they played up in the hook
so if you got to your magnets and lay
them down in your outside drum
around them and everything else it made
them circular
do you think you're going to have a
square you know positive
you know neutral negative or north pole
south
nothing south pole so you've got push
pull
no because your magnetic fields don't
come on and off like that
on a circle they go a different way
and if you apply that to the coils you
make a magnet in a circle under you
build into them
and everything else and hook it up to a
coil
make you get something phenomenal like
they don't even know too much about or
they're not telling you about or they
don't build it to suit
because then you don't get your on or
feels
okay so you understand
so this thing here can be changed and
altered
and stood up a different way
and be a hell of a lot smaller
okay no fighting fields you know there's
different magnets in
in motors you know that don't you that
you can have an alternator or a
generator and everything or magnetic
you know uh field in these things
and you go you know you're fighting on
and off all the time
okay push ball push pull you've got to
go get past that so
to spin them up right you got load all
the time
what about those other ones which are
the same things
but they turn the magnetic fields around
and the
faster you spin them right the freer
they become
what kind of a load did you think you
got on them then you know what i'm
talking about
you spin them and they just become freer
and the faster you spin them the freer
they become
so the faster you spin these the more
load that you've got to put forward
what sort of magnets would you use in
that case
i don't know about any of these things
see this is all
it goes well past me all of all i do is
when i play magnus when i play fields
and everything else i don't
i never read about it i don't know about
me
i don't know the field effects and i
don't know which magnets are which i
don't know how the fields run on them i
don't know any damn thing their deals
peter was saying that they've got a
trick but he can't became demeanor nice
somehow they put him in a certain way
and then you you're bringing back the
normal again which is
something testicular impossible
impossible
these are flat magnets or something huh
right
i normally do this with round ferrites
or round neos
for black because what you do what you
have with a round one is
like i sort of saying with most others
you don't have with round ones
you don't have a start stop understand
you don't have a um you
did you know that they could yeah
do you know that the curve of a magnet
changes the magnetic fields are in
different places
it changes them to a different circle
altogether
it's all right here i'll just look at
the flat ones half and thick three by
three
and another one on the lead absolutely
nuts here
if you're pulling and pushing
these ones you want to flip because
you're not the same
the pole is curved and it's not curved
that way
it's not rounded that's what you can do
with the other one so
shaft like a knee yeah i didn't say i
can't deal with this i'm just feeling
for a sec okay and
so on i've never tried this although
there's a picture of a lot of fingers
you think wants to flick
you come in so far and it wants to
change
the nasty little things they are
this has got a pile of different feels
and what you're doing is
these have got a pile of different
fields on the ends on the sides
have you yeah you do it with round ones
and the round ones have got equal feels
all the way around because it's a circle
this thing is got multitudes as soon as
i rotate it
just changes all the field
okay
did you see that i just pulled
you know you name it and everything else
is um i don't know
i sense i feel i do
well there's only this one well he put
the two